So I'm turning up high and
happens with myự ramen.
I'm slipping away from the moment.
No problem drawing around the world.
I'm burning very selesophantan!
Until step, I'm turning in my face.
Oh
Gear?
Your techniques have changed?
Are you supposed to be a steam engine?
You certainly are full of hot air.
You're starting to test my patience.
The truth is, I'm glad I
met you guys when I did.
Come, come!
What, are you stopping to aim?
That only gives me more time to dodge.
Fine.
Let's see how good your aim is,
then. Shake! Shake, crystal!
Rifle!
Huh?
I can't see him at all!
It's fair!
Missile!
Impossible!
No, it has to be.
The truth is...
I'm glad I met you guys when I did.
He's using the shave technique.
Only CP9 should know the six powers,
but he's clearly mastered it.
Air door!
Huh?
He disappeared.
This is unheard of.
A pirate commanding one of our techniques?
This is a sick joke.
Don't tell me he was
capable of this all along.
No, it doesn't matter.
No one can match the speed
of a true six powers master.
I won't lose to him!
If I turn his body parts
into doors like before,
that should stop him dead in his tracks.
After that, all I have
to do is finish him off.
When we fought before, and it
looked like you were disappearing?
You were really just moving your
feet ten or twenty times a second!
I got the hang of it too.
But I never would have figured
something like that out on my own.
I can take it!
I'll use my strongest defense.
You sure are tough! Aren't you?
All right, then I was gonna save
it, but I have an even better trick.
Don't blink.
I call this...
Man, I'm beat.
Guess my body can't keep this up for long.
Well, I don't care
about my body right now.
I need to move ahead.
Damn it!
What's going on here?
Quick, fire the cannons, man!
Before they step on us!
Yeah, nice try!
Put those pea shooters
on enough to stop me!
You can ride or you can fight, little
bit, but we're coming through either way!
I see it, and I still can't believe it.
I don't know what you said to those guys,
but it must have been something else.
We warriors understand each other.
The time has come, brothers.
The courthouse is looming on the horizon.
Onward!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and go inside already.
The pirates are in the
courthouse, aren't they?
Yeah,
but the problem is there's a big frog at
the door and he's not letting anyone in.
A frog?
Keep hiding, Yokozuna.
Go get him an edge!
We can't stop until the
drawbridge comes down!
If those guys break our line in the
fence, thousands of them can pour in here!
Get out!
Only one of us needs to get through!
Even if everyone else falls, as long
as someone pulls that lever, we've won!
You okay, sis?
Don't worry about me.
All that matters is bringing
down that bridge and
making sure the Straw Hats
get to the Tower of Law.
Hold it!
You're not going anywhere!
Oh, yeah? Try it! Stop it!
What are those pirates plotting?
Why is it so important
for them to go upstairs?
Huh?
You won't get an answer out of me!
We'll see about that,
but I tell you one thing you're
gonna pay if you hurt our big bro!
After them!
Bring those pirates down!
How many of these stupid guards are we
gonna have to beat before they catch a hint?
There they are! Attack!
Hey, if you have to throw them,
at least don't throw them at me!
Would you guys shut up?
I'm trying to think here.
Must have taken a wrong turn somewhere.
You want us to take Franky and Nico
Robin to the Gates of Justice now?
Yes! Do it! Quickly!
But we're way ahead of schedule.
The escort ship isn't even ready yet.
I don't care.
We can just wait for it on
the other side of the gates.
If we get rid of those two, the pirates
won't have a reason to fight anymore.
There's no point in risking
another battle with those
monsters when we have the
power to end this right now.
And while you're at it, gather
all the members of CP9, too. Sir!
Now, it seems as if your one-way trip to
hell will be departing ahead of schedule.
Then we'll have all the time in
the world to deal with your friends
Those pirates sure know how to
bring the party, don't they?
I don't know if they have common
sense, but they sure as heck have guts.
Just you wait and watch, Chimney!
In the end,
whether they live or die, that straw
hat boy and all of his little friends?
Are going to shake things
up the whole world over!
In hundreds of years, nobody's
pulled a stunt like this one.
Mark my words,
when this battle is over,
every man, woman and child is gonna
know the name of Straw Hat Luffy!
Robin!
Yeah, you made it!
Luffy...
I'm here to save you!
Chief Spandam, sir!
There's a man in a straw
hat standing on the
courthouse rooftop who's
shouting things at Nico Robin.
I wasn't able to confirm his identity
up close, but I assume it must be Luffy.
On the rooftop?
How could that happen when I saw
Pluno up there just a second ago?
I thought he was keeping watch.
That idiot.
What the hell is he doing?
Guess I've been running around a lot, huh?
And time for a snack.
Good thing I came prepared.
Me time!
I knew putting these in my
pockets was a good idea.
I just wish I had more pockets.
So that's him, Haas, Straw Hat Luffy.
But what the hell is going on here?
If Bluno was up there, he should've...
It can't be.
No, he couldn't have.
Bluno's a member of CP9, a six powers
master with Devil Fruit powers, no less.
His power level is superhuman.
All right, ready for round two.
How could that scrawny
brat ever defeat him?
Chase Fondam, sir, how should we proceed?
Lucci, where is he?
Somebody call him now,
and the rest of CB9, too.
I've heard enough.
I won't be satisfied until they wipe out
Straw Hat and everyone
in his wretched crew.
No!
While you're at it,
tell Baskerville that if he lets
the Straw Hats lower that bridge,
I'm going to send all
three of his heads rolling!
Yes, sir!
Hey, get that chin up, Nico Robin.
You know, most people wouldn't
come here to save their friends.
Hell, most people couldn't
even make it here at all.
Don't get me wrong.
I know the only reason you agreed to the
government's terms was so
you could protect them.
But you saw what happened.
They don't give a damn about keeping
their word to you or anyone else.
The deal is shot.
Even if you keep your end of the
bargain, it's not going to help anyone.
Only thing left is to wait for your
crew to break you out of this dump.
Doesn't sound so bad to me.
And yet, here you are,
looking as miserable as ever.
I get the feeling you're running from
something even your friends don't know about.
I Wouldn't worry about the
Straw Hats dying in this place.
But if you can't look him in the eye in
the end, they won't be able to save you.
Well, whether you like it or
not I'm gonna make you face.
Listen up all of you we're putting Nico
Robin out of Straw Hats reach immediately.
Come with me to the Gates of Justice.
Bring the prisoners.
But, but chief.
No buts, just do it.
Well, uh, there's one giant
butt that's a big problem.
What the hell is that?
Oh, hey, Spanda.
Like you said, I'm pretty much screwed.
So I figured I might as well
blow myself up, you know?
What?
That way at least I get to take
your sorry ass with me when I go.
You fool.
Wait a minute, will you?
If my butt goes off, the explosion's
going to be at least a mile wide.
Not much point in running,
but you might as well try.
I don't know what's going on in
your pants, but please make it stop!
Three, two...
Damn it, I can't die in a time like this!
One...
Stop it!
Time to go, Robin.
Coo-dip!
Good.
The chains are broken, too.
We're following!
You burn!
That was a close one.
Good thing that fence was
there to catch us, huh?
Hey, you didn't get hurt, did ya?
If I had another bottle of cola,
I could get us to the other
side with a coup de vin.
Hey, check it out.
Straw Hat's over there.
Now's your chance.
Better give him your answer.
He tricked us! Chief!
Franky and Nico Robin broke the
chains and went out on the balcony!
Then what are you waiting for stupid?
Capture them already.
If you let them get away, I'll
send you all to the gallows!
What?!
Hey! Robin!
You're still there!
Didn't you hear me yelling?
Reef...
Don't let them get away!
Grab them before they run!
I don't have time for you thugs right now!
Weapons left!
I guess that means Frankie's there, too.
Okay, I'll be right over.
It's a little far, but I can make it.
Come, come!
Stop it!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm not coming back.
I'm not part of your crew anymore.
Just go away.
I don't want to see your face ever again.
Don't you understand?
Why did you come to save
me in the first place?
Why can't you just let me go?
You never asked for this.
You've gone too far.
For the last time.
I don't want you here.
Do you hear me I just want to die.
Now this is entertainment what a twist!
What the hell are you trying to pull your
friends put their lives
on the line to come here?
And you...
They decided to do that on their own.
Are you kidding me?
Who cares?
You're in the way.
What's wrong, Kaku?
Fitting your anger?
Because your Devil Fruit
powers are so lame?
Oh, shut up already.
I like my powers just fine.
Oh, all this ruckus for one little pirate.
Yo-yo!
Alone though he may be, his
perseverance is certainly admirable.
I'll be damned so he beat Bluno after all.
Ha-ha-ha! What a fool!
Being a barkeep for five years probably
didn't do his fighting skills any favors.
So it would appear, but
it's still a surprise.
Either way, he lost! Cha-ba-ba!
I'm glad you could all make it, CP9.
And just in time, too.
It seems the Straw Hats
are having a little tiff.
It's quite amusing.
You really shouldn't miss it.
Kiddo?
Good work out there, Yokozuna. Keep it up!
guilty guilty yes it's a
guilty cherry step aside
it's time for that frog
to I hear it's verdict.
Guilty.
Guilty!
Ugh, just what we need, more weirdos.
Guilty, guilty!
Let's get him, Chopper.
Wait, I mean go get him, Chopper.
What, me, alone?
I got to admit, I never thought there'd
be an actual judge on this island.
I heard that the people who get taken
here are already considered guilty.
So the Marines just lead the poor saps
to an empty court without even stopping.
I'm afraid you're mistaken, pirate.
On the contrary,
this courthouse carries the integrity
of the greatest authority in the world.
Even scum like you are given
a trial by jury. However!
The jury here consists
entirely of former pirates who
have been condemned to death
row in this very courtroom.
Therefore, their only desire is
to drag others down with them.
This place really is the gate
to the underworld, isn't it?
Thus, in all the trials
carried out on this island...
Not once has any criminal
been found not guilty.
Oh, no!
Guilty!
Damn, they're too strong!
We can't give up now!
If we don't bring down that
drawbridge, it's all over!
Remember, Straw Hat is the one
who's gonna rescue our bro!
If we can't help him with this,
then we have no right to call
ourselves the Franky family!
Yo, Garzana!
You took all those blows, Truss,
and never punched an inch!
I'll beat you!
Don't bother!
We've still got 6,000 marines!
Now, let's storm the courthouse!
Let's crush those pirates!
What's going on why the
Giants here it's the
frog what's the situation
here wait I know you
You're with the straw
hats what do you do with
those Giants can't believe
he held off all those
Marines on his own yeah
he's one hell of a frog
where'd
they
run off to
they must Have gotten lost
again we don't have time
for this crap oh yeah
as long as I go Everything
should work out fine.
Chatsumaki!
Huh? What?
We better keep moving!
You pirates really aren't a
league of your own, aren't you?
You're even strong enough
to order giants around.
It's almost scary, really. Hmm?
Well, uh...
Oh, by the way, your other crewmates
are headed to the roof right now.
The roof?
You should go meet them.
Leave that one to me.
I'll get you there in a flash. Huh?
You want to die?
That's right.
wait a second chief
why are we listening to
this crap and we could
just go over there and
pound that guy's face in patience patience
here we have a captain
who risked his life to
save one of his crewmates only to have his
precious hopes dashed
at the very last second
how tragic and yet i
can't tear my eyes away
it's too amusing robin
i don't know what to say
Wow, could he be more pathetic?
I gotta see the look on his face.
Sorry, but that sounds dumb to me.
He's picking his nose.
Listen, that won't work.
We're already here and
it was a lot of trouble.
We're going to go ahead and save you.
Landed.
And if you still want to die
after we're all back together,
well, that's your choice.
Ow, ow, ow.
Looks like you landed on your head.
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
What the heck happened back there?
I think I might have an
idea of who to blame.
There we go, that was a lot easier
than dealing with those stupid stairs.
Theory is?
I knew it was you!
You're lucky we got
out of the way in time.
If that thing had hit us head
on, we'd be dead right now!
Oh, you're here too.
I'm the first one here no
doubt i've left robin waiting
long enough time for her prince
to moss head what are you
doing here you're gonna ruin
everything finally made it
huh you get lost or something
don't you dare don't even go
Oh!
It's Sniper King!
What?
He's flying! Awesome!
Where's he been all this time?
How is he supposed to land?
Look at that.
The gang's all here.
Yoyoy!
Quite the show indeed!
Stop it, yay!
Although they may be
our sworn adversaries,
to have come this far is
truly quite impressive.
This isn't funny anymore!
Just go away!
Come on, Robin, work with me here.
You can say what you want.
If you want to die or
whatever, that's fine.
But when you say it, you
say it as part of our crew.
Yeah, Robin, he's right!
Come back, Robin!
Hey, Sniper King, can you stand? Hm?
Uh, yeah, of course.
A fall like that won't stop me.
Really, I'll be fine.
From now on, leave everything to us!
I don't have to say that I
didn't know how to say it.
I was trying to find out
what I was looking for.
I was living while I was
living while I was looking for.
I was looking for one light.
I felt like I saw?
If you follow me, the
future will run away.
Every time, every time,
I'll stop laughing and tears.